

Ing. Arch.

MICHAELA

RUDOLFOVA

PROFILE

From an Architect to a Frontend developer? Several reasons led me to change my field. I found myself in frontend development. I enjoy learning new technologies and improving the ones I already use. I like the visual environment with the logical and readable code behind.

In conclusion, I enjoy the community of people in IT who are friendly and helping each other. My heart beats for the ReactGirls community, which has been with me since the beginning of my career change.

CONTACT

+ 420 728 442 119

michaela.rudolfova@seznam.cz

EDUCATION

ARCHITECTURE AND URBANISM

/2011 – 2017, Prague - Dejvice / MASTER 'S DEGREE CTU, FACULTY OF ARCHITECTURE

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML CSS GIT

JAVASCRIPT TYPESCRIPT

REACT GRAPHQL

TAILWIND FIGMA

WEBFLOW ADOBE

WORK EXPERIENCE

VS POINT - FRONTEND DEVELOPER

06/2019 - now, Pernerova 635, Prague

I tried what it's like to work in a bigger office. I became part of a team working on a larger development of apartment buildings near Liberec. The most popular project I was working on in the office is the reconstruction of the winter stadium in Opava.

WEB: https://www.vspoiont.cz/

FREELANCER - FRONTEND DEVELOPER

11/2017 - 03/2019, Mickiewiczova 235/5, Prague

In Patrik Hoffman's studio, I independently led a project for the reconstruction of a villa in Ořechovka with a change of use to dental surgeries. My job was to make an architectural study in dozens of variants, to develop a project for a

http://reactgirls.com http://zixkomix.com/ http://vitrdoplachetproeleonorku.com/ http://fitnut.com/ http://oenergetice.com

STUDIO QARTA - ARCHITECT

06/2019 - now, Pernerova 635, Prague

I tried what it's like to work in a bigger office. I became part of a team working on a larger development of apartment buildings near Liberec. The most popular project I was working on in the office was the reconstruction of the winter stadium in Opava.

https://www.qarta.cz/

STUDIO HOFFMAN - ARCHITECT

11/2017 - 03/2019, Mickiewiczova 235/5, Prague

I independently led a project for the reconstruction of a villa in Ořechovka with a change of use to dental surgeries. My job was to make an architectural study in dozens of variants, to develop a project for a building permit together with the coordination of other professions and negotiations with the authorities. Part of my work was the author's supervision of the construction.

http://atelierhoffman.eu/

WORKSHOPS

REACTGIRLS / 2020 - now

ReactGirls community accompanies me throughout my new career path. It started with participating in a mentoring program with result in the new ReactGirls website written in React and designed in Figma.

In addition to regularly participating in meetups, this year I helped with the Javascript and React coaching of the autumn academy. At one of the meetups, I also gave a lecture on the topic of Work on travels.

CITY DEVELOPMENT 2015

The workshop was focused on development, financing issues, legal aspects and the architectural-urban concept. It pointed to the issue of cooperation between 3 main entities - developers, architects and the city.

PERSONAL SKILLS

Reliability, independence, diligence, openness, willingness to learn new things, creativity

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH - B2

INTERESTS

Gastronomy, travelling, architecture,